"use strict";

module.exports = {
  up: async (queryInterface, Sequelize) => {
    await queryInterface.bulkInsert(
      "savedquestions",
      [
        {
          id: 1,
          question: "Which country is most populous?",
          column: "population",
          correct: "Saudi Arabia",
          rating: 3.5,
          ratingCounter: 4,
          option1: "Belgium",
          option2: "Saudi Arabia",
          option3: "Uzbekistan",
          option4: "Somalia",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 2,
          question: "Which country has the most cell phones per person?",
          column: "phones",
          correct: "Ireland",
          rating: 3,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "Japan",
          option2: "Finland",
          option3: "Uzbekistan",
          option4: "Ireland",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 3,
          question: "How many people live in Sweden?",
          column: "population",
          correct: "10365705",
          rating: 3,
          ratingCounter: 2,
          option1: "10365705",
          option2: "15181925",
          option3: "493559",
          option4: "10638536",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 4,
          question: "Which country is most populous?",
          column: "population",
          correct: "Belgium",
          rating: 5,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "Slovakia",
          option2: "Belgium",
          option3: "Cuba",
          option4: "Latvia",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 5,
          question: "What is the cost of living index of Zambia?",
          column: "costOfLivingIndex",
          correct: "31.72",
          rating: 4,
          ratingCounter: 2,
          option1: "31.72",
          option2: "33.35",
          option3: "55.3",
          option4: "71.78",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 6,
          question: "Which country is the smallest by total area?",
          column: "area",
          correct: "Belize",
          rating: 4,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "Vietnam",
          option2: "Belgium",
          option3: "Ethiopia",
          option4: "Belize",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 7,
          question: "In what continent is Croatia?",
          column: "continent",
          correct: "Europe",
          rating: 5,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "Europe",
          option2: "South America",
          option3: "Asia",
          option4: "North America",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 8,
          question: "Which country is the most densely populated?",
          column: "populationDensity",
          correct: "Kuwait",
          rating: 4,
          ratingCounter: 2,
          option1: "Kuwait",
          option2: "Denmark",
          option3: "Thailand",
          option4: "Montenegro",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 9,
          question: "Which country is most populous?",
          column: "population",
          correct: "Philippines",
          rating: 5,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "South Africa",
          option2: "Jordan",
          option3: "Montenegro",
          option4: "Philippines",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 10,
          question: "What is the crime index of Turkey?",
          column: "crimeIndex",
          correct: "39.49",
          rating: 5,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "58.92",
          option2: "39.49",
          option3: "29.29",
          option4: "35.08",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 11,
          question: "Which country is the smallest by total area?",
          column: "area",
          correct: "Luxembourg",
          rating: 5,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "Germany",
          option2: "Bangladesh",
          option3: "Japan",
          option4: "Luxembourg",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
        {
          id: 12,
          question: "How many people live in Albania?",
          column: "population",
          correct: "2862427",
          rating: 5,
          ratingCounter: 1,
          option1: "1910400",
          option2: "17070135",
          option3: "287025",
          option4: "2862427",
          createdAt: new Date(),
          updatedAt: new Date(),
        },
      ],
      {}
    );
  },

  down: async (queryInterface, Sequelize) => {
    await queryInterface.bulkDelete("savedquestions", null, {});
  },
};
